cityfile.com 2011-05-25

# Cityfile: Privacy Policy

Cityfile Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Cityfile") is committed to protecting the online privacy of visitors to our website. The privacy policy set forth below (this "Policy") applies only to the website and online services provided by Cityfile. The purpose of this Policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our website, how we may use that information, and how we disclose it to third parties.

1\. Information That We Collect

 _Personal Information  
_

At various locations on our website, such as in registration forms, surveys, and polls, we may request that you supply us with "personal information," such as your name, email address, mailing address, home or work telephone number. Although you do not have to provide us with any information to visit our website, you may not be able to fully utilize all of the services on our website if you choose not to provide certain information. If you do choose to give us personal information through our website, we will collect and retain that information.

 _Non-Personal Information  
_

When you use our website, we may also collect "non-personal information." We consider "non-personal information" to be information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you personally, such as demographic information (your age, gender, income, education, profession, zip code, etc.). Non-personal information may also include technical information, such as your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the websites you visit immediately before and immediately after you visit our website, and other anonymous data involving your use of our website. Non-personal information may also include information that you provide us through your use of our website, such as the terms you enter into the search functions of our website.  We reserve the right to use or disclose non-personal information in any way we see fit.

 _Cookies  
_

We use "cookies" to enhance your visits to our website. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not store personal information about you, unless you knowingly provide it. Cookies can store non-personal information, such as what websites, pages, or advertisements your browser has accessed. We use cookies to store information and personalize your experience with our website. For example, cookies allow our website to recognize your browser as a previous visitor, and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while you were previously browsing our website. Our cookies can also store your password, personalize pages, and keep track of any selections you may make.

You do have control over cookies. Most browsers can be set to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. Most browsers can also be set to refuse to accept cookies, although this may affect your Internet experience. You can also erase cookies that are already on your computer. For more information about working with cookies, you should consult your user manual, FAQ, or "help" function of your specific browser and operating system software.

 _Web Beacons  
_

We also may use "web beacons" (also often referenced as "clear GIFs," "clear pixels," "web bugs," "1x1 GIFs," or "1x1 pixals") which are tiny graphic image files, imbedded in a web page in GIF, jpeg or HTML format, that provide a presence on the web page and send back to its home server information from your browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the web beacon is located, the type of browser that is accessing the site and the ID number of any cookies on your computer previously placed by that server.  We may use web beacons to collect non-personal information about your use of our website and the websites of selected sponsors and advertisers, and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information collected by web beacons allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our website and selected sponsors' and advertisers' sites. Our web beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our website or those of our sponsors'. We do not link non-personal information from web beacons to personally identifiable information without your permission.

2\. Use of Information We Collect

 _Our Services and Website  
_

We use your personal information to provide to you any services that you may request or require, to communicate with you and to allow you to participate in online surveys. We use aggregated non-personal information about our users to understand our website's demographics, such as the percentage of male and female users, the geographic distribution of our users, the age ranges of our users, a combination of these or other demographics. We may also use the personal or non-personal information we collect to analyze how our website is being used and to improve the content of our website.

 _Email Communications  
_

If you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. However, aside from our reply to such an email, it is not our standard practice to send you email unless you request a particular service that involves email communications, you otherwise consent to being contacted by email and to send you information about products and services which we believe may be of interest to you. 

3\. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

 _Aggregate Information  
_

Except as specifically set forth in this Policy, we do not share your personal information with any non-affiliated third party without your permission. We may disclose aggregate information, such as demographic information, and our statistical analyses to third parties, including advertisers or other business partners. This aggregate information does not include your personal information.

 _Affiliates and Non-Affiliates  
_

We restrict access to personal information to Cityfile employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We may, however, share your personal information with certain websites that are controlled by us, or by entities under common control with us (our "Affiliates"), so that they and we can offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. Please refer to our Affiliates' privacy policies for details regarding how they handle your personal and non-personal information.

 _Service Providers  
_

We sometimes engage unaffiliated businesses to assist us in providing you certain services. For example, we may use third parties to provide advertising, marketing and promotional assistance, provide email services, or facilitate our online services. In those instances, we may need to share your personal information with them. We require these companies to use your personal information only to provide the particular product or service and do not authorize them to use your personal information for any other reason.  
We sometimes offer promotions in conjunction with a third party sponsor. If you choose to participate in one of those promotions, we may share your information with the sponsor if they need it to send you a product or other special promotion they offer.

 _Business Transactions Involving Cityfile  
_

As Cityfile continues to develop, we may buy or sell all or part of our business or assets or combine with other businesses. If so, personal and non-personal information that we or other businesses have collected will likely be transferred as part of the transaction. If we sell a business, we will attempt to ensure that requests made of us regarding email communications will be honored.

 _Third Party Advertisers  
_

We use third-party advertising companies to deliver specific advertisements to you, which appear on pages throughout our website. These companies collect non-personal information about your visits to our website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may also aggregate your non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research, and other similar purposes. These companies may place their own cookies on your computer. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting and using this information, you may visit each third party advertiser's website directly and opt-out.

 _Other Disclosures  
_

We may disclose personal information when we are required or requested to do so by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; to enforce or apply our rights and agreements; or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Cityfile, our users, or others.

4\. Children
